monsterlearning.com 2005-12-17

# 

**Privacy Policy — Your Privacy Rights**

**Overview**  
MonsterLearning is committed to protecting the privacy of our users. We want to provide a safe, secure user experience. We will use our best efforts to ensure that the information you submit to us remains private, and is used only for the purposes as set forth herein. 

**Information About All MonsterLearning Visitors**  
In general, we gather information about all of our users collectively, such as what areas users visit most frequently and what services users access the most. We only use such data anonymously and in the aggregate. This information helps us determine what is most beneficial for our users, and how we can continually create a better overall experience for you. We may share this information with our partners, but only in the aggregate, so that they too may understand how MonsterLearning visitors use our site, so they may create a better overall experience for you, as well. 

**Information About You Specifically**  
In some instances, when you sign up to receive more information about a college or university, we may need more specific information about you, such as name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number, type of computer, etc. If you give us permission, we may use that information to make you aware of additional products and services that may be of interest to you or to contact you regarding site changes. 

During your visit to MonsterLearning, we may also ask you for other information, such as information on your interests, your likes and dislikes regarding the site, the types of schools you are interested in, etc., in an effort to deliver to you the best possible site experience. 

During the school search process, and at certain points thereafter in connection with school searches, MonsterLearning asks you whether information about you may be sent to third parties who have products, services and opportunities which may be useful to you. MonsterLearning understands how important your information is to you. Therefore, MonsterLearning does not share any information that can be tied to you without your permission. 

**General Information Disclosure**  
Except as described in this privacy policy, we do not disclose information about your individual visits to MonsterLearning, or personal information that you provide, such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, credit card number, personal references, etc., to any outside parties, except when we believe it is required by law or to protect MonsterLearning, our users or others. But, we may record and share aggregated information with our partners. Also, if you input your information on a co-branded registration page, such as that of a college or university information request page, then your information becomes the property of both MonsterLearning and the partner school. In that instance, the use of your personal information by our partner school will be subject to the privacy policy of that institution and MonsterLearning is not responsible for their use of your personal information. 

We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples may include hosting our web servers, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These other companies will have access to your personal information as necessary to perform their functions, but they may not share that information with any third party. 

**Cookies**  
To enhance your experience at MonsterLearning, we use a feature on your Internet browser called a "cookie". Cookies are small files that your Web browser places on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies for remembering user names and passwords and preferences, tracking click streams, and for load balancing. Because of our use of cookies, we can deliver faster service, consistent, updated results, and a more personalized site experience. You have the option of setting your browser to reject cookies. However, doing this will hinder performance and negatively impact your experience on our site. 

**Feedback**  
MonsterLearning has an area on the site where you can submit feedback. Any feedback that is submitted through this area becomes the property of MonsterLearning. We may use this feedback, such as success stories, for marketing purposes, or to contact you for further feedback on the site. 

**Children**  
We do not specifically collect information about children. We believe that children should get their parents' consent before giving out personal information. If you are concerned about your child's use of MonsterLearning, we encourage you to use Web filtering technology to supervise your child's access to the site. We also encourage you to participate in your child's experience with MonsterLearning. With a little guidance, the site can prove very useful in finding a part time or summer job for your child, as well as providing them with excellent career counseling information. 

**Privacy Commitment Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy commitment for MonsterLearning, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about MonsterLearning's privacy commitment, please feel free to email us at [notification@Monster.com](mailto:notification@Monster.com) or call 1-800-MONSTER and speak to one of our representatives. 

Thank you for using MonsterLearning. We'll keep working hard to earn your loyalty. 

Updated February 2, 2004
